DCinside
기타미드갤러리 나엘남캐
닐 S. 브레이스 센터
- 호놀룰루 -
자기가 테이프 감으면
운이 안 좋대요
You know it's bad luck
to tape your own hands,
and you... you want to wrap it a
little thicker over your knuckles.
관절 쪽은 더 두껍게
감아야 될 거에요
오른손은 제가
도와줄게요
Let me help you out
with that right hand.
You know how to do this?
- 어떻게 감는지 알아?
- 네, 무예타이도 좀 했고
Yeah, did Muay Thai, little jiujitsu.
- 유도도 했어요
- 정말?
Really?
Yeah.Used to spar with my ex-boyfriend.
네, 예전 애인이랑
스파링도 했었는데
It was kind of fun until
I started beating him.
제가 이기기 시작하니까
재미 없다던데요
Maybe you should be going out
into that ring instead of me.
나 대신 링에
올라가지 그래?
지금 포기해도
안 늦었어요
It's not too late to call it off.
나가서 코가 망가지면
못생겨 보일 텐데..
It's not gonna look so hot
if your nose is over here.
- 나 격려하는 거 맞지?
- 아마도요
I'm sorry.Are you... you
paying me a compliment?
Maybe.
주먹 쥐어봐요
세게..
Okay, make a fist.
Tight.Okay.
- Hey, McGarrett?
- Yup.
- 맥개럿!
- 응
- You're up.
- All right.
- 준비해
- 응
- 한 번만 더 쳐줘
- 네
- One more for luck.
- OK.
- 쇼타임이에요
- 쇼타임..
- Showtime.
- 말려 본 거 맞지?
- 말려봤어요
You did try and talk
him out of it, right?
- Yeah, I did.Didn't really work.
- Clearly.
- 안 먹히던데요
- 그랬겠지
저런 사람이라니..
Oh, not that guy.
이거봐라,
완전 좋아보이네
Oh, look at this.This is perfect.
- 뭐해?
- 죽기 전에 수건 던져라
- What are you doing?
- Getting ready to throw in the towel before you die.
- 구강 보호대 줘
- 구강 보호대라고?
- Mouth guard.
이럴 땐
헬멧을 써야지
You need a helmet, not a mouth guard.
- 다 됐어
- 이겨요
- Ok.
- Get get 'em.
여기 서세요
Guys, come here.
질문 없죠?
Any questions?Let's go.
시작 합시다
준비 됐죠?
Are you ready?Are you ready?
시작!
Let's fight!
*******
Hawaii Five-O 2x06
Ka Hakaka Maika'I (The Good Fight)
Original Air Date on October 24, 2011
알렉스 오로린
스티브 맥개럿
스콧 칸
대니 윌리엄스
대니얼 대 킴
친 호 캘리
그레이스 박
코노 칼라코아
마시오카
맥스 버그만
나엘남캐 한글자막
수정금지 / 자유배포
Hawaii
Five-O Season 2 Episode 6
******
- Loco Moco from Rainbow?
- Yes, sir.
- 그 집 로코모코야?
- 그렇습니다
제 것도
챙겨 오셧겠죠?
Hope you brought enough for everyone.
NCIS 특수요원
켄지 블라이야
Special Agent Kensi Blye from NCIS's Los
Angeles Office, this is Steve McGarrett.
LA 지부에서 왔지,
여긴 맥개럿이네
- 반가워요, 선장님
- 반가워요, NCIS?
- Nice to meet you, sailor.
- Nice to meet you.
- NCIS, huh?
- Yup.
샘한테 이번엔
진짜 고기 사줄테니까
You tell Sam that I haven't forgotten
about that steak dinner I owe him,
먹고 싶으면
여기로 오라고 해요
but he got to come out
here to collect, okay?
일단 저부터 먹고
전할게요
I'd start saving up.Man
can put away the protein.
- 하나 드세요
- 고마워요
- Here, you can take this one.
- Thank you.
맛있겠네요
Oh, nice.
그건 왜
보고 있어요?
What are you doing with that?
영상 분석하는데
도움이 필요했어
I needed help analyzing the footage.
조 얘길 들어보니,
제임슨 주지사와
According to Joe, this meeting between
Governor Jameson, Wo Fat and your father
우 팻이랑 아버님이
만난 영상이
was recorded by a surveillance camera in
Governor Jameson's office over a year ago.
당시 현장에서
몰래 찍혔다던데요
지금까진 내용을 몰랐겠죠
소리가 뭣 같아서..
Only you have no idea what he's
saying because the audio sucks.
음성 파일은 복구가
안 된다는 거지
What she means is, that the
audio file is unrecoverable.
내가 블라이
요원을 불렀어
I flew Agent Blye in from L.A.
독순술에 능하고
믿을 수 있는 사람이야
She's an expert lip
reader, and we can trust her.
진심이세요?
You sure about that?
제가 알아야
되는 거라도?
Is there something I should know?
Um, basically, I owe Joe one.
사실, 제가 조한테
빚을 져서요
제가 자카르타에서
곤란할 때 도와주셨으니..
He pulled a few strings and got me out
of a sticky little situation in Jakarta,
so, uh, yeah, you can trust me.
믿어봐요
You weren't supposed to be in Jakarta.
- 거기 있으면 안 됐잖아?
- 그건 비밀이었거든요?
제가 거기 있는 건
비밀이었는데요?
You weren't supposed to
know I was in Jakarta.
이해했다
Point taken.
- 음식 이름이 뭐라고요?
- 로코모코야
- What is this called again?
- Loco Moco.
볶음밥이랑 햄버거 패티,
계란 후라이랑 소스야
It's a mixture of rice, hamburger, couple
fried eggs and gravy.
따로도 괜찮은데
같이 먹으니 죽이네요
Separate--delicious.Together--heaven.It's
great.
- 뭐 나온 건 없어요?
- 아, 네
Yeah, it's good.Listen, have
you got anything yet?
Right.Um, so I managed to
decipher some of the conversation.
판독 하려고
영상을 좀 수정했어요
서로 인사를
주고 받고요..
They exchanged pleasantries.
주저리 주저리
떠들다가..
And... small talk, small
talk, small talk until... here.
바로..
여기에서
- 아버님이 질문을 하는데요
- 무슨 말이요?
- Your father says something that gets a reaction.
- What did he say?
아버님이..
'쉘번에 대해 알고 싶다'
- He says, "I want to know about Shelburne."
- Shelburne?
쉘번?
그리곤 우 팻이
대답하는데..
And then your man Wo Fat responds by
asking, "Who told you about Shelburne?"
'누가 그걸 말 해줬어?'
And that's when your father turns
around, and I can't see what his response is,
이 때, 아버님이
돌아서서 안 보이지만
쉘번이 나올 때
우 팻은 긴장했어요
- but Wo Fat clearly tensed up at the word "Shelburne."
- Shelburne.
쉘번이라..
That mean anything to you?
기억 나는 거 없어?
- 네
- 저도요
- No.
- Me, neither.
사람 이름이나
거리명인가?
Well, could be a name
of someone, or a street?
무슨 암호일 수도 있죠
It could be a code for something.
I don't think so.I ran it through Naval
Encryption Database and didn't get anything.
해군 암호망을 조회하니
아무것도 안 나왔어요
마코토가 알려 줬으니
뭔지 알지도 몰라요
Mokoto led us to this video.Maybe
he knows what Shelburne is.
마코토가 누구죠?
I'm sorry.Who's Mokoto?
참.. 제 보안허가
5등급이거든요?
Really, guys?I've got level
five security clearance.
말 안 해줘도
조회 할 수 있어요
I can run his name whether you tell me who
he is or not, so are we gonna do this or what?
- 자카르타는 왜 갔어요?
- 이거랑 관련 없어요
Why were you in Jakarta?
Another story, another day.Anything you
tell me about Mokoto stays between us.
모코토 얘기는
우리 비밀로 할게요
모코토가 주지사를
조사하는데
Mokoto hired my father to
investigate Governor Jameson.
저희 아버질
고용했어요
응, 대니
Yeah.Danny.
바로 갈게
I'll be right there.
사건이 생겨서
가봐야 해요
I caught a case.I got to go.
정말 고마워요,
알로하
Thanks for the help, okay?Aloha.
알로하,
아침 고마웠어요
Aloha.Mahalo for the breakfast.
제가 봤을 땐
포기 안 할거 같네요
Something tells me he's
not going to let this go.
안 되는데
No.
디아몬드 헤드
- 호놀룰루 -
*****
Vic was Jake Griffin.
피해자는
제이크 그리핀이야
- 그 식당 사장?
- 응, 유명하지
- The restaurant guy?
- Yeah, one and only.
식당이 여긴 다섯 개
본토엔 20개나 있어
Five restaurants in
Hawaii, 20 on the mainland.
이런 데 살려면
생선구이 많이 팔아야겠다
Oh, you got to sell a lot of misoyaki
butterfish to buy a place like this, huh?
너 이 사람한테
생선으로 맞았냐?
Never would have pegged you
as a butterfish type of guy.
No, I'm not.I'm really not.
안 맞았어
어차피 돈도 없어,
근데 그레이스가
My wallet is not, either, but I weaned
Grace off of fish sticks onto butterfish,
하도 튀김을 좋아해서
생선구이를 먹였는데
and now it is her
favorite, so that's good.
이젠 제일 좋아한데
그래서 참 행복해
- 좋은거지
- 맞아
- It's good.
- Yeah.
수영장 관리인이
의자에 총을 맞은 채
Pool guy found the body duct-taped to a
chair, single gunshot wound to the chest.
- 묶여 있던 걸 봤대
- 나온 거 있어?
- What we got, Lori?
- Body was dumped in the pool.
시체가 수영장
안에 있었어요
염소처리 된 물은
증거를 지우는데
Unfortunately, chlorinat water is quite
effective at eliminating trace evidence.
되게 효과 있거든요
- 편리했겠네
- 사전에 계획 했나봐
- Oh, that's convenient.
- Or premeditated.
하지만, 피해자의
입 주변 화상자국과
However, based on the size of the contact
muzzle burn and at the entry wound,
총알이 관통한
부분을 보면
I would hazard a preliminary
guess that the victim
제 추축으로는
피해자가
was shot with a .38 caliber
handgun at point-blank range.
38구경 권총으로
바로 앞에서 맞은 것 같아요
경찰에선
살인 흉기 찾았대?
HPD turn up a murder weapon yet?
Not yet.They're inside processing.
- 아직 조사중이에요
- 강도사건이었나?
It looks like a robbery gone bad.
네 생각은 어때?
How you think this went down, Lori?
이런 사건에서
가장 위험한 순간은
Well, usually, the most dangerous
time in an encounter like this
피해자가
제압당하기 전이에요
is before the victim's restrained, 'cause
usually that's when a struggle can happen,
보통 그 때
저항을 하니까요
but what bothers me about this is, Jake
was already duct-taped to the chair.
근데 이미 묶어놓고
왜 죽였을까요?
그래서 범인은
안심 했을 거란거지?
All right, so he poses no
threat, he can't fight back.
- 이유를 알아야 겠네?
- 응
- So, why shoot him?
- Yeah.
루빈 탐 작품이
몇 개 사라졌고
Several Reuben Tam paintings taken.
보석, 은제품..
Jewelry, silverware, electronics.
텔레비전도
뭘 훔치려는지
목표가 확실했구만
Okay, so, these thieves definitely
knew what they were after.
경찰에서 최근에
강도사건이 또 있었대
Yeah, HPD says there were other home
invasions in Honolulu this week.
- 같은 솜씨로?
- 응
- Same M.O.?
- Yeah.Minus the dead guy in the pool.
거기는 사람만
안 죽었어
All right, let's call HPD,
그러면 경찰에 연락해서
다른 사건도 확실히 알아보자
let's make sure we know everything there is
to know about these other home invasion cases.
그래
Yeah.
Our victim-- he
have a family?
피해자가
가족도 있었어?
이혼했고, 아내는
본토에 가 있대
He's divorced.Wife's on the
mainland.They got one kid.
아들은 여기 사는데
14살 조쉬야
Josh, 14.Lives here.
여기산다고?
지금 3시 15분이야
Lives here, huh?It's 3:15.
- Yeah.So?
- School let out 15 minutes ago.
- 그래서?
- 3시에 학교 끝나잖아
대니, 어디가?
Hey, Danny, where you going?
워.. 조쉬
Josh.Hey, buddy.
- 안녕
- 무슨 일이에요?
What's going on?Why are all
these police at my house?
왜 경찰들이
우리집에 있어요?
- 아저씬 대니 형사야
- 아빠는 어딨어요?
Son, I'm a detective.My
name's Danny Williams.
Where's my dad?
Come here.
따라오렴
조쉬는요?
Where's Josh?
- 제 조카 어딨죠?
- 여동생분 되시나요?
I need to see my nephew.
- Jake's sister?
- Yes.I'm Samantha.
- 전 사만다에요
- 조쉬는 괜찮나요?
- Is Josh okay?
- He's fine.He's with one of our detectives.
괜찮아요, 저희 형사랑
같이 있습니다
누가 널 보러왔구나
There's someone here to see you, buddy.
조쉬!
Josh.
맙소사..
Oh, God.
괜찮아.. 괜찮다
It's gonna be okay.It's gonna be okay.
오늘 라크로스 채를
만들었다던데..
Kid makes the lacrosse team today.
아빠한테 빨리
자랑하고 싶었나 봐
He can't wait to come
home and tell his pop.
우리가 꼭
범인을 잡을 거야
Danny, we're gonna find
the people who did this.
파이브 오 본부
*****
이 사건 둘 다
어떻게 된거야?
All right, these other two home
invasions-- what do we got?
지난 5일간
상류층 집에서 일어났고
Well, both took place within the last five
days in the same upscale neighborhoods,
비슷한 솜씨였지
both with the same M.O.
마스크 쓴 네 명이
집 안에서 가족을 기다렸죠
Four masked gunmen were waiting
for the families inside their homes.
강제 침입한
흔적은 없고요
No signs of forced entry.
These guys duct-taped the men to chairs and
beat them in front of their wives and children
남자를 의자에 묶고
아내랑 애들 보는 앞에서
엄청 값나가는 물건
위치를 댈 때까지 팼어
until they gave up the location
of their valuables-- unreal.
제이크는 혼자였잖아?
조쉬도 학교에서 안 왔고
Right, but Jake Griffin was alone, right?
Josh had not come home from school yet.
인질이 없었으니까
상황이 심각해졌나 보죠
Mm-hmm, maybe that's why the situation
escalated.I mean, they had no leverage.
피해자가 맞서 싸운
이유이기도 하고요
Maybe that's why Jake fought back.
애초에 이 사람들이
당한 이유는 뭘까?
Yeah, maybe, but why were these
people targeted in the first place?
두 가족다
공통점이 있을 거야
What's the link?There has to be a link.
보통 가정집
강도범들은
Well, typically home invaders have been inside
their victims' homes prior to the attack.
피해자의 집에서
먼저 기다리죠
They use that opportunity to
assess their victims' assets.
그 시간에 피해자의
재산을 평가하는 거에요
그러면 가정부나
배달원 같이
All right, so then we cross-check
maids, contractors, deliveries--
집에 올 수 있는
사람들을 조사해 볼게
anyone with access to their homes.
Yes, start with that.
그것부터 해봐,
우린 피해자랑 만나서
We'll talk to the victims, see if they remember
anything they forgot in the statements.
진술 과정에서 빼 먹은거
있나 물어봐야 겠어
이전에 다 말했어요
저흰 기억나는 게 없어요
We already told the other
detectives, we don't remember anything.
Okay, sometimes being back
in a specific environment
사건 전에 있었던 일을
생각해 보시면
that you were at just prior to
a trauma can trigger a memory.
아마 기억이
날지도 몰라요
다른 피해자와
두 분 사이에 같은 점은
The only thing that you and the
other victims have in common was
최근에 와이키키
고급 식당에서
that you all ate at high-end Waikiki restaurants
in the days leading up to the attacks.
식사를 하신 거
뿐이에요
일주일에 최소 한 번은
이용하시잖아요
Restaurants that you
frequent at least once a week.
저희도 돕고 싶어요
근데..
Look, we want to help, we do, but
I was duct-taped to a chair
절 의자에
테이프로 묶어놓고
and had a gun put to my head
in front of my wife and kids.
가족 앞에서
제게 총을 겨눴어요
- 그 이상은 기억 안나요
- 이해합니다
- I don't remember much beyond that.
- Understand.
우리 애들은 자기가
죽는지 알았대요
My kids thought they were going to die.
이러한 폭력을
경험하게 되면
When a violation of
this kind takes place,
the experience can be
extremely traumatic.
정신적 충격이
굉장할 수 있어요
시간이 좀 걸려도
극복하실 겁니다
It'll take some time, but
you will get past it.
떠올려보세요,
식당에 도착했을 때나
Try and think back to when you were
arriving or when you were leaving.
떠날 때를요,
마주친 사람은 없어요?
Do you remember anybody
bumping into you?
길을 물었다던지
핸드폰을 빌린 사람이요
Ask you for directions, use your phone?
그런 일은 없었어요
No, nothing like that.
지갑을 다른 데
둔 적은요?
Did your purse ever leave your side?
제가 볼 수 있게
항상 의자에 올려놔요
No, I always keep it on
the table so I can see it.
차는요?
- What about your car?
- What, what about it?
- 차가 뭐가요?
- 어디에 주차하세요?
- Where'd you park?
- Uh, down the street.
길가에다 하는데요
아니야,
당신 기억 안 나?
No, you didn't.Remember, honey, we
were running late and you valeted.
우리 바빠서
발레 맡겼잖아
No, I parked......
아니,
내가 주차를..
잠깐만..
당신이 맞아
Wait, um, you're right.I
gave my car to the valet.
발레 요원 한테
맡겼어요
Do you keep your house
keys on the same key chain?
차 키랑 집 키랑
같이 두세요?
네, 그건 왜요?
I do.Why do you ask?
*****
We'll be in touch, but call
us if you remember anything.
기억나는 거 있으면
연락주세요
고마워요
- Thank you.
왜?
What's up?
Danny, is there a valet stand
out the front of that restaurant?
거기 식당 앞에
발레 주차대 있어?
Yes, there is.Very bright orange
and yellow sign-- Kokua Valet.
응, 보인다
되게 밝은 주황, 노랑색에
'코쿠아 발레' 라는데
그 쪽도 있구나
Let me guess--
you, too.
방금 공통점을
찾은 거 같아
Yeah, I think we just found our link.
이 업체는
그 일대 식당들이랑
Kokua Valet-- they serviced all
the restaurants where the vics ate,
제이크씨 식당에도
출장을 나와요
including Jake Griffin's place.
Yeah, the company has got 20 freelance
employees on the payroll, but get this--
업체에 등록 된
사람은 20명인데
이걸 봐봐,
이 직원 네명은
four specific employees all worked together
the nights the victims were at the restaurants.
피해자들이 저녁을
먹을 때 일했었어
강도사건 당일 날에
네명 전부 쉬었겠지
Let me guess, all four of 'em were off
the days that the invasions took place.
You got it.
- 맞았어요
- 전과 있는 사람은?
Any of these four got a record?
한 명 있어
Yeah, one.
데이브 록 하트
Oh, Dave Lockhart, proud owner of a string
of petty theft and robbery charges.
좀 도둑질이랑
강도 한 건 하신 분이네
오늘 밤에 일해?
This guy working tonight?
아뇨, 다른 세 명도
안 해요
Nope, and neither are the others.
록 하트, 문 열어!
파이브 오다
Dave Lockhart.Five-O.Open up.
우측
이상 없어
Clear right.
좌측 이상 무,
아무도 없어
Clear left.Room clear.
마지막 방도!
Last room clear.
- 아무도 없어
- 범행 중 일수도
- Nobody's home.
- They could be on the prowl.
Find something?
- 찾은 거 있어?
- 응
Yeah, looks like these guys are taking
impressions of the keys on the job,
아마 일 할 때
열쇠 본을 떠서
여기 와서
복사본을 만드나 봐
then they come back
here, they make copies.
I got molds, I got some
kind of polymer gel.
형틀도 있고
이상한 젤도 있어
분명히 여기
우리 피해자 열쇠랑
All right, I give you ten to
one, we check the victim's locks,
증거물 같은 게
있을 거야
we find trace evidence of this stuff.
그게 뭐야?
What do you got, Chin?
감시 사진이야
Surveillance pictures.
일을 저지르기 전에
사전 조사를 한 것 같아
Looks like our suspects cased all
the houses before they hit 'em.
All right, I know that one.That's
the Laskos', there's Doroughty's.
나 어딘 지 알아,
여긴 라스코씨네 집이고
여기는..
도로시 가족 집
난 여기
모르겠는데, 넌?
I do not recognize this one.You?
몰라
- No.
- Could be there right now.
- 지금 여깄을 수도 있어
- 내가 찍을게
I'll get a picture.
사진에 해는 동쪽에 있고
아이나-하이나 쪽 같아
Sun's to the east.Looks like Aina Haina.
코노, 너한테 방금
사진 보냈어
Yeah, Kono, listen, Chin
sending you through a photo.
어딘지 당장 찾아봐,
지금 범행 중인 거 같아
Find that house for us right away.We
think they could be hitting it.
아이나 하이나
- 오하우 -
*****
가족은 보내줘요!
Just let my family go,
- 닥쳐!
- 제발 해치지 마세요..
- Shut up.
- Don't hurt him, please.
닥치라고!
- Shut up.
- I'll give you whatever you want.
뭐든 다 드릴게요!
닥치라고 했잖아!
No, stop.
금고는 어딨어?
두 번 묻게 하지 마!
Where's the safe?
Don't make me ask you again.
- 몇 명이나 보여?
- 강도범 세 명에..
How many guys are we looking at here?
Looks like we got three home
invaders, no sign of the fourth.
- 네 번짼 안 보이네
- 인질도 넷이에요
Hostage count is four.Two
adults, two children.
어른 둘에 아이 둘,
이미 묶여 있네요
Looks like they're already restrained.
- 레이저 도청 준비됐어
- 어디있는지..
Laser mic is online.
Tell me where it is or
you're all going to die.
- 안 불면 다 죽인다!
- 서재 안 티비 뒤에요..
In the office behind the plasma.
당장 들어가야 해
친 형이랑 로리는
We got to breach and we
got to breach right now.
Okay, Chin, Lori, you guys take the rear.
뒤로 돌아 들어가,
너네 둘은 나랑 가자
You two, you're on me.
All right, come on.
들어가!
- Go, go.
- Clear left.
- 좌 측 이상 무!
- 등 돌려!
Turn around.I said turn around.
등 뒤로 돌려!
이상 없어!
- Room clear.
- Let's see your hands.
Room clear.
이상 없어
손 들어!
Hands, hands, hands.
뒤 돌아서
내 쪽으로 와
Turn around and back up to me.
이상 무!
Clear.
이제 괜찮단다
It's gonna be all right.
다른 사람은요?
Is there anybody else in the house?
Hey!Chin, Lori, number four's
coming to you right now.
친, 로리, 넷째 놈이
그쪽으로 간다
파이브 오다!
꼼짝마!
Five-O!Don't move!
멈춰!
Freeze, freeze!
잘했어요
Nice work.
How many times I got to
tell you, I didn't kill Jake?
몇 번이나 말해요?
제가 안 죽였어요
지금 뭐하는 거야?
What are you doing?Why are you, uh--
are you covering for your crew, huh?
네 동료들
감싸주는 건가?
너희한테
명예는 없잖아
I mean, you know there is
no honor amongst thieves.
Eventually they will rat on you, so why
don't you just beat 'em to the punch?
어차피 딴 놈이 널 팔건데
우리가 먼저 선수 치자고
왔어?
막 시작했는데
- Hey.
You didn't miss anything this guy's vocabulary
does not stray too far from the word "lawyer.
얘가 아는 단어는..
변호사 밖에
없나 봐
어떻게 된거냐?
So what happened?
제이크가 너희들이..
Jake connect the dots,
figure out you were making copies of his
customers' keys and then hitting their homes?
손님들 키 복사해서
강도하는 거 알아낸거냐?
- 변호사
- 저거 봐
- Lawyer.
- See what I mean?
'Cause, you see, this
wasn't a random score.
네 정체를
제이크가 안 거야
- 제이크가 알고 있었지?
- 변호사!
- Jake was on to you, wasn't he?
- Lawyer.
You go to his hale, ask him not to talk to the
cops, and then everything goes out the door.
제이크 집에
찾아가서
신고하지 말라고 했는데
일이 틀어져 죽인 거지?
당신 미쳤어?
그 사람 본적도 없어!
You crazy?I never even met the man.
뭔 소리야, 그 식당
발레요원이 너였잖아?
What do you mean you never met the guy?
You were a valet driver
at one of his restaurants.
내가 바보로 보이냐?
웃기는 소리 하시네
What, do I look like an
idiot?That doesn't make any sense.
아니야, 그 사람은
거의 바지 사장이었어
No, man, the guy's just
a name on a T-shirt.
여동생이
사업을 관리했다고
His sister's the one that
ran the whole operation,
- 남자가 내쫒기 전까지는
- 왜 짜른거지?
- at least until he kicked her to the curb.
- He fired her, why?
How the hell would I know?I
told you, I never met the man.
어떻게 알아?
만난 적도 없댔잖아
우리가 그 집을
털었다고?
Look, you think we hit his house?
훔친 걸 찾아봐
Go through our stash.
제이크란 사람 물건은
보이지도 않을테니까
You won't find a damn thing
from Jake Griffin's place.
그나저나, 변호사!
By the way, lawyer.
검시관 사무소
*****
하도 이상한 걸 찾아서
생각해 봤는데
I called because my
findings were highly unusual
그 수사에
관련 있을 것 같아서요
and I thought they may be
pertinent to your investigation.
잘 됬네요, 제이크
살인 용의자를 잡았는데
Great, because we have a suspect in custody
who swears he didn't murder Jake Griffin.
Oh, how is your sense
of smell, Agent Weston?
- 냄새 얼마나 잘 맡아요?
- 뭐라고요?
Excuse me?
약간의 딸기랑
라벤더향을 감지했어요
I detect a hint of strawberry and
lavender, perhaps even some fresh coconut.
아마.. 신선한
코코넛 향기도요?
- Body wash or shampoo?
- Max, you're creeping me out.
- 바디 워시에요 샴푸에요?
- 맥스, 소름 끼쳐요
Oh, I'm sorry, I wasn't trying
to be forward, Agent Weston.
죄송해요, 앞서 가지
말았어야 됬는데
전 요점을
짚으려고 했답니다
I was merely trying to prove a point.
후각이 법의학 수사를
도와 줄 때가 있죠
Sometimes our olfactory senses
are our best forensic tools.
Okay, olfactory senses.What
are you trying to say?
후각이라..
무슨 생각 인데요?
혹시, 용의자 한테서
희미하게 나는
You didn't happen to notice a faint odor of
Australian tea tree oil on your suspect, did you?
호주산 물레나무 냄새를
맡으셨나요?
굳이 용의자 냄새를
맡으려고는 안 하는데요?
I try not to smell the suspects, Max.Why?
Well, it is just one of several
atypical findings in this case.
몇 가지 이례적인 것 중에
이걸 찾았어요
피해자를 묶고 있던
테이프에서 채취를 했는데
When I swabbed the duct
tape that bound your victim,
호주산 물레나무 기름
흔적을 찾을 수 있었죠
I was able to recover some traces of
Australian tea tree oil and eucalyptus oil
유칼립투스 나무
기름도요
테이프 접착 면에
남아 있었거든요
that was preserved on the
adhesive side of the duct tape.
보시다시피,
그리핀씨 손목엔
As you can see, Mr.Griffin suffered no
trauma or subdermal bruising of the wrists.
외상이나
멍든 곳이 없었죠
피해자가 그 당시
싸움을 벌인게 아니네요
So our vic didn't put up a
fight when he was restrained.
이유도
알 거 같아요
And I believe I know why.
테이프 밑면에서
핏자국을 발견했어요
I found high-velocity blood
spatter under the duct tape,
피해자가
의자에 묶이기 전에
which would suggest that Jake Griffin
was dead before he was taped to the chair.
죽었다는 거죠
Doesn't make any sense-- I mean, why
shoot him and then tape him to a chair?
이해가 안 돼요
왜 쏴놓고 묶어 놓은 거죠?
So it turns out that our
vic's sister, Samantha Martel,
우리 피해자 동생인
사만다 마텔씨가
몇 달 전, 그리핀씨 회사
급여명단에서 빠졌어
was dropped from the Griffin
Enterprises payroll a few months ago.
- 짤린 거야?
- 기록엔 안 나와
What, was she fired?
Nothing in the record that states that.
회사에 연락 해보니
다들 사만다가 직접
When I reached out to the company,
the party line was that Samantha left on her
own to work at Jake's charitable foundation.
제이크 자선 단체에
일을 하려고 그만 뒀대더라
진짜 단체야, 아니면
세금 때문에 세운 거야?
And what, is that legit or is the
foundation just code for tax shelter?
아니야, 그 사람은
평소에도 좋은 일 했어
No, n-no, Griffin did a lot of
good work for the community.
I mean, the guy opened gyms all over
the island to keep kids off the street.
밖에 나도는 애들을 위해
섬 전체에 체육관도 세웠지
의도는 좋은데
수익은 없겠군요
Noble but not as profitable.
그리핀씨 변호사랑
얘기하고 왔는데
So I just spoke to Griffin's attorney.
Um, it turns out his entire estate and
all his restaurants fall to his son Josh
그리핀씨 모든 자산이랑
식당은 아들한테 남겼대
근데 조쉬가
25살이 되어야지 받아
but only after he turns 25.
그 전까지 누가
돈을 관리할 지 알겠다
And until then, I bet I
can guess who's in control.
동생인 사만다지
The sister Samantha.
Yeah, looks like she maybe shot her
way back into the restaurant business.
외식사업에 다시 끼고
싶었을 수도 있지
잠깐만
Excuse me.
- 조?
- 약속 잡았어
- Joe.
- It's set.
내일 오후에 마코토씨
집에서 만나기로
We're meeting Mokoto tomorrow
afternoon, his place, 1600 hours.
16시다
네, 갈게요
Okay, I'll be there.Hey, uh, is
Kensi still with you?
아직 켄지랑
같이 있어요?
방금 공항에
데려다 주고 왔는데, 왜?
No, I dropped her off at
the airport an hour ago.Why?
Oh, I was just wondering.I mean, you guys seemed
to have, uh, you seemed to have quite a past.
그냥.. 궁금해서요
두 분이서 서로..
과거가 좀
있어보이셔서..
스티브, 걔는
내 딸뻘이야
Steve, she's young
enough to be my daughter.
켄지 보니까
두번 째 아내랑 닮았어요
You know something, Joe?She kind
of reminds me of wife number two.
키크고 검은머리에,
치명적이고..
Tall, dark, lethal.Seems to be your type.
그 쪽 스타일
같아서요
미안, 끊는다
Sorry, you're breaking up.
손님을 그렇게 맞이하면
됩니까, 화이트 소령?
Is that any way to welcome
a houseguest, Commander White?
적당히 숨길 곳이
없었다고 인정하세요
You must admit that with the lack of
suitable hiding places in this apartment,
이런..
아파트에요
이 집 향기는
맘에 드네요
you set the odds firmly in my favor.
뭘 원하나?
What do you want?
이미 죽은 사람을
왜렇게 찾는지 알고 싶어요
I want to know why you are asking questions
about men that are no longer with us.
질문은 그만하겠어
I'll stop asking those questions
when you tell me about Shelburne.
네가 쉘번이
뭔지 알려주면
무슨 뜻인가?
What does it mean?
제 생각보다 많이
알아냈네요, 영감님
You've done more work than I
could have imagined, old man.
- 부탁 하나 해도 될까요?
- 그게 뭔데?
Would you do me one favor?
What's that?
존 맥개럿씨 한테
아들도 곧 간다고 전해줘요
Tell John McGarrett that his
son will be along soon enough.
*****
- 조쉬는 어때요?
- 시간이 필요한가 봐요
How's Josh?
He's going to need some time
to heal, but he's a strong boy.
그래도 아빠를 닮아서
씩씩한 아이에요
A lot like his father.
잠시만요
Excuse me.
- 앉으세요
- 감사합니다
- Go ahead.
- Thank you.
수사에 진척은
있었나요?
Has there been any progress in the case?
있어요, 사실은
그것 때문에 왔습니다
As a matter of fact, there
has, yeah.That's why we're here.
마텔 부인, 오빠분
사망시간에 어디 계셨어요?
Mrs.Martel, uh, where were you at
the time of your brother's murder?
오빠 자선단체에서
경찰 전화 받기 전까지
I was working at Jake's charitable foundation
all day, until the police called.Why?
계속 일하고 있었어요,
왜요?
제이크씨 식당을
몇 개 관리하셨죠?
You used to, uh, used to run a couple
of restaurants for Jake, right?
맞아요, 그게
무슨 상관인데요?
Well, yeah, but what does that
have to do with anything?
오빠한테 짤려서
악감정이 있나 싶어서요
Well, I was just wondering if there were any
hard feelings when your brother fired you.
절 짜른게 아니고
제가 관둔 거에요
What?No, he didn't fire me, I quit.
왜 관두신 건데요?
Really?Why would you do that?
I mean, just change
careers out of the blue.
왜 갑자기
직장을 옮기셨죠?
잘 모르시나 본데..
Okay, look, you don't understand.I have always
loved that foundation, working with those kids.
전 항상 자선단체에서
애들을 돕는걸 좋아했어요
자리가 났을 때
오빠가 제의를 했고요
When a position opened up, Jake
offered me a job full-time.
전 이제 식당 쪽은
신경 안 써요
I don't have anything to do
with the restaurants anymore.
이젠 돌아가셨으니
재산을 받으시잖아요
Yeah, that was true yesterday, but now
that Jake's passed, you're in control.
네? 뭐..
What no, that's--
Jake's will?
그게 유언이에요?
조쉬를 돌보라는 거겠죠
That's about taking care of Josh.
어떻게 생각하시든
전 제 오빠 안 죽였어요
Look, I don't care what you
think.I did not kill my brother.
알겠어요
Okay.
실례지만, 혹시
총 가지고 계신가요?
Gonna have to ask
you, uh, Mrs.Martel, do you own a gun?
제꺼는 아니고요
오빠한테 하나 있었어요
Well, I mean, it's not really
mine.Uh, Jake had a gun.
총을 안 가지고
계신 걸로 조회됐는데요
Well, you see, there was nothing
registered in either of your names, ma'am.
등록은 안 돼
있을 거에요
Well, no, it wouldn't
have been registered.
Jake found out that one of the guys
단체에서 돕던 사람이
총을 가지고 있던 걸
that he was helping with his charity
got ahold of a gun, and he took it away.
오빠가 뺏은 거에요
총은 어딨어요?
Where's the gun now?
*****
Hands up.Hands up.
손 올려!
Jake wanted to build a place where
underprivileged kids could come and be safe.
제이크는
이 곳에서..
저소득층 아이들이
안전하길 바랬어요
All of these kids can
come and train for free.
아무나 여기 와서
무료로 훈련받을 수 있게요
마텔 부인,
Hey, Mrs.Martel.
여기 사인 좀
할게 있어요
Just need you to sign a couple things.
뭐야, 너
장 보러 왔냐?
What, you in the market
for some cleaning products?
선수들이 훈련을 끝내고
이런 걸로 몸을 닦아
Fighters use these to
wipe down after they train.
Uh, kills ringworm, staph, MRSA.
피부 튼데나..
어디 감염되지 말라고
Hey, look what they're made from.Australian
tea tree oil and eucalyptus oil.
여기 성분을 봐봐
호주산 물레나무 오일과
유칼립투스 오일이네
Those are the same oils that Max found
on the duct tape he pulled off our vic.
피해자를 묶고 있던
테이프랑 성분이 같아
응, 갈게요
Yeah.We're good.
그래, 잘 했어
All right, good job.
총은 여기 있어요
Jake's gun's right in there.
자기야, 괜찮아?
Honey, is everything all right?
- 총이 필요하다셔
- 뭐하러?
- They need the gun.
- For what?
- 이걸로 오빠를 쐈다나 봐
- 뭐?
- They think that I killed Jake.
- What?
마텔씨, 잠깐
물러나 계세요
Mr.Martel, I'm going to ask you
to just step back, all right?
총이 없네요
No gun.
무슨 소리에요?
여기 있어야 되는데
What-What do you
mean?It's got to be there.
Well, it's not.When was
the last time you saw it?
없잖아요
마지막으로
총을 본게 언제죠?
몰라요..
아마 몇 주 전에?
I don't know, maybe a couple weeks ago.
Hey, it's all right.You didn't
do anything wrong.All right?
괜찮아, 자기가
잘못한 거 없어
알았지?
두 분 말고 이 총을
아는 사람이 있나요?
Okay, um, who else knew about
this gun, besides you two?
Just Jake and I.Well, and Boriero.
제이크랑 저랑..
보레로도 알아요
- 그게 누구에요?
- 우리 선수에요
- Who's Boriero?
- One of the fighters who trains here.
오빠가 걔한테
총을 뺏었거든요
That's the kid I mentioned.
Jake took the gun off of him, said
that if he wanted to train here,
여기서 훈련 하고 싶으면
말썽부리면 안 된다고요
he had to stay out of trouble.
That was one of Jake's
only rules about this place.
그게 오빠가 유일하게
지켰던 규칙이에요
Okay, fine.Where's he at?Is Boriero here?
혹시 보레로
지금 여기 있나요?
몇 주 전부터
여기서 연습 안 해요
- No, he hasn't trained here for a few weeks.
- Why is that?
왜요?
He left after an argument with my brother about
going pro, said that he wanted a sponsorship.
프로 진출 때문에
제 오빠랑 싸웠거든요
보레로는 스폰서쉽을
달라고 했는데
But Jake said that the
foundation wasn't about that.
오빠는 자선 단체니까
안 된다 했죠
그럼, 보레로 집은
어디죠?
- All right.
- You know where Boriero lives?
빅터 보레로
Vitor Boriero.He went away in 2009
for taking part in an armed robbery.
09년에 무장강도에
가담해 감옥에 갔어요
He strong-armed the owner of a Kapiolani
beer joint and then cleaned out the safe.
맥주집 주인한테
폭력을 썼더군요
지금은 갱생을 했고요
실제로 보면
부드러운 남자겠지?
This guy sounds like
a complete gentleman.
82년식 지프, 검정색
CJ-7 모델을 몰아요
Guy drives an '82 Jeep CJ-7, black.
It should give you
heads up if he's home.
집에 있으면
차도 거기 있을 거에요
- 내가 운전 또 해?
- 알았어, 고마워
Am I driving? Of course I'm driving.
- All right, thanks.
-Oh, and one more thing.
잠깐, 이거 하나
알고 가세요
Word to the wise: Boriero's trained.I
would not engage him hand-to-hand.
보레로는 선수에요
무기 없이 덤비지 말아요
그러진 않을 거야
난 총을 좋아하거든
That's not going to
happen.I like my gun.
저기 차가 있네
집에 있는 것 같아
There's the Jeep.Looks like he's home.
도둑 맞을 걱정도
안 하는구만
Doesn't look like Boriero's
worried about theft.
That's one of the benefits
of being built like King Kong.
완전 킹콩이라서
걱정 없나 보지
- Not gonna believe this.
- What do you got?
- 안 믿겨진다
- 뭔데?
똑똑한 놈은
아니었어
He's obviously not very bright.
훤한 곳이야
Plain sight.We have a
beautiful .38 caliber.
이게 그 아름다운
38구경이야
살인 도구랑
똑같은 구경이지
Same caliber as the murder weapon.
어이!
- Hey!
- Hey.
What you guys doing?
- 당신들 뭐해?
- 파이브 오다!
Boriero, Five-O.Show me
your hands right now.
당장 손 들고
엎드려!
Get on the ground.On the ground.Hey!
엎드려, 야!
안 돼!
No, no, no, no!No, no, no, no!Come on!
하지 말라고.. 참!
문으로!
Door, door!
My shoulder, my shoulder!
어깨, 내 어깨!
- 내 어깨!
- 응?
My shoulder!
내일 경기가 있다고
I was supposed to fight tomorrow, man.
Yeah, plenty of chances to fight
where you're going, Boriero.
넌 가는데 마다
싸우려고 하냐
- 왜 도망쳤어?
- 내가 뭘 도망쳐
- You're going away, you understand?
- Going away for what?
We found Jake's murder
weapon in your Jeep.
제이크 살인 흉기를
네 차에서 찾았어
내 총 아니야
너희가 심었겠지
You know that gun ain't
mine.You planted it.
You good?
괜찮아?
- 응
- 괜찮다고?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
무기 없이
덤비진 말랬잖아
"Do not engage in hand-to-hand."
Do you remember that?
- 기억 안 나?
- 까먹었나봐
- I must've forgot.
- Must've forgot it.Okay.
아, 까먹으셨구나
- Hey, tell me something.
- What?
- 뭐 좀 물어보자
- 뭐?
맥스가 피해자
사망시각 언제랬지?
When did Max say the time of death was?
오전 9~10시
사이, 왜?
Uh, between 9:00 and 10:00 a.m.Why?
얘가 죽인 게
아니잖아
'Cause this guy didn't do it.
According to this, you were in
the hospital yesterday morning.
여기 보면, 어제 아침
병원에 있었던데
그래
Yeah.
전날 연습 때
머리를 세게 맞아서
I was sparring the night before, took a head
punch.Figured I should get that checked out.
검사 받으러 간거야
맞아서 머리가 나빠진 게
아니면 좋겠다
All right, well, I hope that the head punch
didn't mess with your memory too much,
- 질문할 게 있거든
- 내가 죽였다고 생각해?
because we got some
questions we want to ask you.
You really think I killed Jake?
How do we know this isn't
just a stab at an alibi?
알리바이를
꾸민 거 아냐?
I might be able to fake a
wristband, but you can't fake a CT scan.
CT 찍은 건 못 속이지
병원에 전화해봐
- Call the hospital.
- Oh, we got somebody doing that.
벌써 하고 있어
그동안 그 총이 왜
네 차에 있었는지 말해봐
In the meantime, why don't you tell us
how the gun that killed Jake
Griffin ended up in your jeep?
차가 열려 있으니,
누가 갖다 놨겠지
Jeep's wide open.Anyone
could have planted that.
- Why would someone do that?
- Why would I shoot Jake?
- 그럴 사람이 있나?
- 뭐하러 제이크를 쐈겠어?
그 도장 아니었으면
아직도 노숙하고 있었어
Without that gym, I'd
still be on the streets.
글쎄, 오랜 버릇은
쉽게 안 없어지지
I don't know.Old habits die hard.
제이크는 날 보고
루저랬어
Jake called me a loser to my face.
누구도 감히 말 못했지만
맞는 말이었지
Not many men have the
stones to say that to me,
but he was right, and
I respected him for it.
- 나도 제이크를 존중했고
- 스폰서 문제 이후론
I believe that.You did respect him,
up until the point where he
wouldn't give you a sponsorship.
- 존중 안 했겠지
- 다 틀렸어
You got it all wrong.
요즘 이종격투기는
돈이 많이 되지
Lot of money in MMA these days.
프로로 가면
시청료도 얼마 받고
I mean, you turn pro, you get a
couple of pay-per-view fights.
- 돈이 많이 되겠지
- 제이크는 관심 없었고
We're talking about a lot of money.
It's a lot of money, but Jake
was not interested in that.Right?
자선 사업이 그렇게
되는 게 싫었던 거야
He didn't want his charity
to turn into a business.
You guys fought over it, and when
it did not go your way, you shot him.
서로 싸우고
네 생각대로 안 되자,
- 네가 쐈겠지
- 미친 소리야!
That's crazy!
프로 가고 싶었어
누구든 가고 싶겠지
Look, did I want to go
pro?Sure.Who wouldn't?
난 마샬 제안도 거절했는데
계속 졸랐단 말이야
But I turned down Marshall's
offer, but he wouldn't let it go.
제이크 처남?
무슨 일이었는데?
Oh, Marshall?Jake's brother-in-law--
what does he have to do with this?
날 전부
밀어준다고 했어
He said he'd train
me, manage me, the whole shot.
Even asked me if I could recruit
a couple of the other guys, too.
나보고 다른 애들을
모아 달라고도 했어
커미션은 얼마나
떼어 달랬어?
How much commission was he asking for?
20퍼센트
20%.
그 사람 마지막으로
본 게 언제야?
20%.When was the last time you saw him?
어제 나한테
제이크 얘길 하러 왔어
He came by yesterday to
break the news about Jake.
직접 말해주고
싶었다면서
Said he didn't want me to hear it on TV.
네 차도
그 때 있었어?
Was your jeep parked in
front when he came by?
응..
Yeah.Always in the same spot.
항상 같은
자리에 놓지
마샬 마텔을
알아봤는데요
All right, so I looked into
Marshall Martel like you asked,
and I found something very interesting.
뭐 하나 찾았어요
According to his credit card statement,
카드 내역을 보니
어제 아침 사건 현장에서
yesterday morning, he spent $84 at a hardware
store five blocks from the crime scene.
가까운 공구점에서
84달러를 썼어요
이것 좀 보세요
Check out what he bought.
테이프랑
청소도구에요
Duct tape and cleaning supplies.
시간을
확인 해 봐요
Check out the time stamp.
10시 17분
10:17.
That's right around TOD.
사망 시각에
가깝네
One, two.One, two, three.
One.One.One, two.
저기요!
마샬?
Hey!Marshall!
- Hang on.Just finishing up.
- No, you're all finished.Come on, you're done.
- 곧 끝낼게요
- 너야말로 끝장이다
5분 휴식
Do five.
What are you talking about?
무슨 소리에요?
제이크 그리핀을
네가 죽였잖아
Talking about the fa that
you killed Jake Griffin.
- 뭐라고요?
- 먼저 공구점에 들려서
- Excuse me?
- Yeah.
Then you went to the hardware
store to cover up the crime,
증거를 지우려고 했잖아
좋은 시도 였어
which is a good indication to me that
you weren't planning on killing him.
지금까진
잘 몰랐거든
Right, but when you did, you wanted
the cops to be looking the other way,
살인을 저지르고
경찰을 혼란시키려고
so, you covered it up
티비에서 본
강도 사건이랑
and made it look like one of those home
invasion crimes you saw on the news.
비슷하게
꾸몄던 거야
무슨 일이에요?
What's going on?
손 뒤로 돌려
어서..
Hands behind your back.Come on.
마샬, 왜
체포되는 거야?
Marshall, why are they arresting you?
말 좀 해봐!
Marshall, say something.
- 죄송하게 됬어요
- 말 좀 해보라고!
- Samantha, I'm sorry about this.
- Marshall, say something!
마샬?
Marshall?!
사고였어
It was an accident.I was
just trying to scare him.
- 겁만 주려 했는데
- 내 오빠잖아..
What?He was my brother.
He had all the money in the world.And all
I wanted was a little something for us.
돈도 많으니까
우리 조금만 도와달라고..
Something so that we wouldn't have to
come to him with hat in hand anymore,
더이상 구걸 안 하게
조금만 도와 달랬는데
- but he just wouldn't listen.
- So, what, you killed him?
- 내 말을 안 들었어
- 그래서 죽였니?
서로 다투다가
매형이 총을 찾길래..
We were arguing, he went for the
gun, it went off, and I... I panicked.
겁을 먹었어
미안해
I'm sorry.I'm sorry.
미안해..
정말 미안해
I'm so sorry.
지나갈게
Excuse me.
- Oh, yeah.
- Pardon me, wahine.Excuse me, brother.Pardon me.
미안해 아가씨,
미안해 형씨
다들 좀
나눠줘라
Sure, make sure everybody
gets some, brah.Yeah.
Kona.
자리도 좋네?
Oh, good seats, huh?
Oh, yeah.
너한테도 그 팝콘은
많아 보인다
That is, um, a lot of
popcorn, even for you, Kamekona.
난 강냉이 먹을래
Oh, give me some kakimochi.
압력으로 튀긴거야
몸에 좋다고
Air-popped.Healthy kind, sistah.
안 배고파?
You guys hungry?
먹어 보죠, 뭐..
Don't mind if I do.
좀만 가져가!
Oh, easy, brah!No more refills over here.
여긴 리필
안 된다고
I know this is for charity, but this
is crazy.Right?Even for McGarrett.
자선 행사라도
이건 미친 짓이야
아무리
맥개럿 오빠라도
그래서 상대선수..
So, his opponent...
전적이
여기 써있는데
It says in his statistics here that he's
21 and eight, with 13 TKO's.at's a TKO?
21승 8패래요
TKO 13번은 뭐에요?
13명은 다쳐서
더 싸우지도 못 했단거지
It means that 13 of his opponents
were unable to continue fighting him.
그럼 좋은 건가요?
Oh, so that's a good thing then?
맥개럿 한텐
안 좋지
Not for McGarrett.
들어봐요
Okay, listen.Listen, the mantra is, "This is
all for charity." Okay, so you have to say it.
자선 행사 뿐인 걸
잊지 마요
그니까..
포기하고 싶으면
- I'll be fine.
- Okay.
- 난 괜찮아
- 네
맥개럿?
Yo, McGarrett?
나 대신 나가줘서
고마워
Thanks for taking my spot on the card.
제이크라면
못 나가게 했을 텐데
Jake wouldn't want the
fans cheated out of a fight.
It's all for the kids, brah.
애들을 위한거잖아
널 위해서
노력해볼게
I'll try to put on a good show for you.
내가 네 어깨도
부러뜨렸는데..
Besides, I'm the one who
dislocated your shoulder.
잊은거 아냐
Yeah, I didn't forget.
Hit 'em hard, bro.
빡세게 해
- Excuse me, Miss.
- Yeah, thanks.
- 가볼게요
- 네
좋아요..
All right.
방금 경기는
여기까지였고요
******
********
하와이, 호놀룰루에
계신 여러분들
시간이 됬습니다!
오늘 저녁
메인 이벤트입니다
*********
Okay, that's your cue and
your last chance to back out.
지금이 마지막으로
포기 할 기회야
너 좀..
Would you...?
냉혈한 사나이
척 리델..
현지 출신인
상대 선수는요
스티브 맥개럿!
됐어, 내려와
Okay, stay down!
집에 가자
내려오라니까
Let's go home.You want
to go home?Stay down.
자선 행사잖아
일어나지 마
It's charity.Don't get up.
Stay down.
- Go!
- Yes!
Come on!Come on.
끝내줬어
Oh, you the man.
I didn't know an arm could
bend that far back, brah.
팔이 그렇게
멀리 나갈진 몰랐어
사실, 어깨 관절은
굉장히 자유로워요
Actually, the rotator cuff has
an amazing range of mobility.
그렇게 다쳐선..
You want me to get you
a steak for that eye?
자선 행사가 이렇게
아픈지 누가 알았겠어?
Right?Who knew charity hurt so much?
Boss, when you got back up, and
went after that guy, it was pure...
아까 일어나서
되받아 쳤을 때는..
- 완전..
- 완전 '전사' 였지!
Pure imua, brah!
사실 바보라는 뜻인데
우리가 놀려먹는 거야
That means pure stupidity, and
we're all in agreement.
What you got going on
with that hand there, Danno?
- 손에 붙인 건 뭐야?
- 너 때려 줄려고
I figured while you're at it, bring it.
덤벼
의자 치우고
한판 붙어
*****My money's on the SEAL.
난 SEAL 요원 한테
걸거야
I'll take that
action, Danny's one scrappah.
- 진짜 보고 싶다
- 대디는 한 주먹감이야
모코토씨 집으로
당장!
*******
Joe.
왔어요
무슨 일 있었어요?
모코토씨는요?
What happened to you?Where's Mokoto?
죽었어
He's dead.
- 죽어요, 뭔 일인데요?
- 도착해보니까..
Dead?What happened?
I got here.Door was
open, his body's in the study.
문이 열려 있었고
서재에 시체가 있었어
고문 당한 것
같더구나
Looks like he was tortured.
네?
What?!
Who would torture an
old man in a wheelchair?
휠체어 탄 노인을
누가 고문해요?
우 팻..
Wo Fat.
이해가 안 돼요
여긴 왜 왔죠?
I don't understand.Why-Why
would he come here?
- 마코토는 어떻게 알고요?
- 우 팻이 날 찾아왔어
How did he know about Mokoto?
Wo Fat paid me a visit last night.
뭔 소리에요?
What are you talking about?
나한테 덤비더니,
사라졌더라
Got the jump on me, and
then he disappeared.
- Did you tell him about Mokoto?
- No... but he must have known.
- 모코토 얘길 한 거에요?
- 안 했어
그래도
알아차린 것 같아
알았어요
Okay.
입단속을 한 게 아니면,
질문이 있어서 그랬겠죠
Wo Fat's either cleaning house, or
he's looking for answers, right?
우리 탓이야
We did this.
- What?
- Our questions got Mokoto killed.
우리 호기심 때문에
모코토가 죽은 거라고
안 돼요, 우 팻이
시작한 거에요
No, Joe.Wo Fat started this.
저는 끝까지
갈 거고요
But I plan to finish it.
돌아 가면서
곰곰히 생각해 보거라
You continue to go down this
road, son, you got to ask yourself,
얼마나 많은 목숨이
더 희생되어야 하는지
how many more lives is that gonna cost?
나엘남캐 한글자막
수정금지 / 자유배포
Hawaii
Five-O Season 2 Episode 6